<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Big Data Analytics with R</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Big Data Analytics with R</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Database &amp; SQL</title>
      <link>/post/2018-04-29-database-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-04-29-database-sql/</guid>
      <description>Database &amp;amp; SQL This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Date Time Lecture Notes Readings Day1 Session 1 Introduction Session 2 Basic R Session 3 Using github Session 4 Functional Programming Day2 Session 1 Data Structure &amp; Tidy Data Session 2 Data wrangling with dplyr Session 3 Web Scraping Session 4 Shiny and Rmarkdown Day3 Session 1 Parallelization Session 2 Database &amp; SQL Session 3 Bigish Data Day 4 Session 1 SparklyR Session 2 Real World Data Science Topics 소</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Note: Due dates of exams and project will not move, however the timeline of topics and smaller assignments might be updated throughout the semester.  Date Title Slides   Day1 Welcome to Data Science     Lab 00: Logistics    Day2 Lab 02: Logistics     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> First Name  Last Name  E-Mail  City  State AL CA IL      Send   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>